Contact

amyltaylor@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amyltaylor123 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Nursing Clinical Research

Amy Taylor

Director Of Nursing at Advantage IR

Austin, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Cardiac Catheterization Laboratory Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Patient Safety, and Acute Care. Strong healthcare services professional with degrees focused in Registered Nursing and Radiologic technologist.

Experience

Advantage IR
Director Of Nursing
July 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Cedar Park Regional Medical Center Cath Lab RN March 2018 - July 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Boston Scientific
Peripheral Clinical Specialist
April 2016 - March 2018 (2 years)
Austin, Texas Area

St. David's HealthCare RN August 2012 - April 2016 (3 years 9 months)

OU Nursing - Life Stage Solutions Cardiovascular Technologist January 2005 - July 2012 (7 years 7 months) Oklahoma City, Oklahoma

United States Air Force Radiologic Technologist November 1998 - November 2004 (6 years 1 month)

Page 1 of 2

Oklahoma City, Oklahoma

Education

Rose State College

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2012)

Page 2 of 2